

# **EISENPOL MANALO**

- **t**. + 639763093148
- Eisenpol27@gmail.com
- in www.linkedin.com/in/eisenpol -manalo-857802248
- San Roque, Marikina City, Philippines, 1801

#### **EDUCATION**

Bachelor of ScienceIn Information Technology

**Rizal Technological University** 2022 - Present Boni Ave, Mandaluyong city

Dee Hwa Liong Academy
2020 - 2022
Pasig City

High School Diploma
San Roque National High School
2016 - 2020
Marikina City

## **SKILLS**

Canva

Figma

CSS / HTML

UI / UX Design

Laptop Troubleshoot & Upgrades

MS Word

## **ABOUT ME**

Hello there! I'm Eisenpol Manalo, a passionate UI/UX Designer currently immersed in the world of Information Technology at Rizal Technological University. I believe in the power of design to shape meaningful user experiences that seamlessly blend functionality and aesthetics.

### **EXPERIENCE**

**Q** 2022 - 2023

UI Design & System Development

Led the design initiative for a mobile application project, crafting an intuitive user interface, and website design prototype. Implemented a streamlined ordering system through proficient utilization of C++ programming.

2017 - 2018 San Roque National Highschool

6 Basic Film Editor

Contributed significantly to the school presentation of 'Florante at Laura' by overseeing the filming and direction of key scenes. Additionally, played a pivotal role in the post-production process by single-handedly editing the entire movie.